Guide to the George Ellery Hale Papers HaleGE
California Institute of Technology Archives and Special Collections
- Personal Correspondence and Papers Relating to Individuals, 1865–1950; 1; 20 linear feet (Tape HaleGE_01, Carton 1, Reel 1–40, Carton 3)
  - Mabel B. Messer, 1910–1922; HaleGE_01_00_028_09; 69 pages (Box 28, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 69 to 138.
  - Dayton C. Miller, 1922–1933; HaleGE_01_00_028_10; 21 pages (Box 28, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 139 to 160.
  - John A. Miller, 1930; HaleGE_01_00_029_01; 10 pages (Box 29, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 161 to 171.
  - Robert Andrews Millikan, 1915–1944; HaleGE_01_00_029_02; 545 pages (Box 29, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 172 to 717.
  - E. A. Milne, 1929–1934; HaleGE_01_00_029_03; 13 pages (Box 29, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 718 to 731.
  - Charles S. Minot, 1901–1912; HaleGE_01_00_029_04; 9 pages (Box 29, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 732 to 741.
  - Miscellaneous, 1899–1940; HaleGE_01_00_029_05; 72 pages (Box 29, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 742 to 814.
  - Miscellaneous documents given to Rodman Paul by Margaret Scherer, HaleGE_01_00_175_01 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Includes letters by Hale, Millikan, G. Abetti, Louise Carnegie, E.G. Watson, M. Huggins, and Walter Adams, as well as a diary kept by Evalina Hale, photographs, and a passport.
    This file has not been digitized.
  - S. A. Mitchell, 1899–1931; HaleGE_01_00_029_06; 29 pages (Box 29, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 815 to 844.
  - William Mitchell, 1909; HaleGE_01_00_029_07; 6 pages (Box 29, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 845 to 851.
  - Prince of Monaco, 1919–1921; HaleGE_01_00_029_08; 11 pages (Box 29, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 852 to 863.
  - Charlotte E. Moore, 1931; HaleGE_01_00_029_09; 3 pages (Box 29, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 864 to 867.
  - E. C. Moore, 1918–1919; HaleGE_01_00_029_10; 9 pages (Box 29, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 868 to 877.
  - E. H. Moore, 1897–1930; HaleGE_01_00_029_11; 178 pages (Box 29, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 878 to 1056.
  - H. D. Moore, 1904–1905; HaleGE_01_00_029_12; 4 pages (Box 29, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 1057 to 1061.
  - Paul Moore, 1936; HaleGE_01_00_029_13; 11 pages (Box 29, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 1062 to 1073.
  - P. H. Morgan, undated; HaleGE_01_00_029_14; 1 pages (Box 29, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 25, frames 1074 to 1076.
  - Thomas Hunt Morgan, 1925–1938; HaleGE_01_00_029_15; 273 pages (Box 29, Folder 15, Box 30, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 20 to 293.
  - F. R. Moulton, 1903–1919; HaleGE_01_00_030_02; 23 pages (Box 30, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 294 to 317.
  - Mt. Wilson Bulletin, 1923–1924; HaleGE_01_00_030_03; 4 pages (Box 30, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 318 to 322.
  - Mt. Wilson correspondence, 1901–1937; HaleGE_01_00_030_04; 52 pages (Box 30, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 323 to 375.
  - Mt. Wilson early bills and insurance policies, 1903–1924; HaleGE_01_00_030_05; 134 pages (Box 30, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 376 to 511.
  - Mt. Wilson insurance and taxes, 1904–1910; HaleGE_01_00_030_06; 57 pages (Box 30, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 512 to 569.
  - Mt. Wilson instruments, buildings, diagrams, etc., 1904; HaleGE_01_00_030_07; 71 pages (Box 30, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 570 to 641.
  - Mt. Wilson material for annual report, 1926–1935; HaleGE_01_00_030_08; 66 pages (Box 30, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 642 to 708.
  - On Mt. Wilson site, etc., 1903–1904; HaleGE_01_00_030_09; 28 pages (Box 30, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 709 to 737.
  - Seeley W. Mudd, 1917; HaleGE_01_00_030_10; 5 pages (Box 30, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 738 to 743.
  - D. S. Mulvin, 1917–1927; HaleGE_01_00_030_11; 56 pages (Box 30, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 744 to 800.
  - J. P. Munroe, 1901–1907; HaleGE_01_00_030_12; 15 pages (Box 30, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 801 to 816.
  - W. B. Munro, 1928–1934; HaleGE_01_00_030_13; 14 pages (Box 30, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 817 to 831.
  - Capt. Lee Murphy, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_030_14; 6 pages (Box 30, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 832 to 838.
  - Sir John Murray, 1912; HaleGE_01_00_030_15; 7 pages (Box 30, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 26, frames 839 to 847.
  - H. F. Newall, 1901–1937; HaleGE_01_00_030_16; 518 pages (Box 30, Folder 16, Box 31, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 20 to 538.
  - Simon Newcomb, 1897–1935; HaleGE_01_00_031_02; 175 pages (Box 31, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 539 to 710. It also includes four pages which were misfiled in the microfilm edition as reel 38, frames 118 to 120 and 122.
  - Ernest F. Nichols, 1900–1925; HaleGE_01_00_031_03; 71 pages (Box 31, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 711 to 782.
  - E. L. Nichols, 1900–1925; HaleGE_01_00_031_04; 12 pages (Box 31, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 783 to 795.
  - Seth B. Nicholson, 1923–1931; HaleGE_01_00_031_05; 4 pages (Box 31, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 796 to 800.
  - Alfred Noyes, 1917–1941; HaleGE_01_00_031_06; 5 pages (Box 31, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 801 to 806.
  - Arthur Amos Noyes, 1901–1916; HaleGE_01_00_031_07; 515 pages (Box 31, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 27, frames 807 to 1323.
  - Arthur Amos Noyes, 1917–1936; HaleGE_01_00_032_01; 573 pages (Box 32, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 20 to 593.
  - W. A. Noyes, 1914–1919; HaleGE_01_00_032_02; 21 pages (Box 32, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 594 to 615.
  - Frau O. E. Obermayer, 1920; HaleGE_01_00_032_03; 5 pages (Box 32, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 616 to 620.
  - Donald O'Melveny, 1930; HaleGE_01_00_032_04; 1 pages (Box 32, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 621 to 622.
  - Henry Fairfield Osborne, 1901–1935; HaleGE_01_00_032_05; 227 pages (Box 32, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 623 to 849.
  - W. F. Osgood, undated; HaleGE_01_00_032_06; 5 pages (Box 32, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 850 to 855.
  - W. Osler, 1911–1919; HaleGE_01_00_032_07; 6 pages (Box 32, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 856 to 862.
  - Sir Richard Paget, undated; HaleGE_01_00_033_01; 1 pages (Box 33, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 863 to 864.
  - J. A. Parkhurst, 1903–1925; HaleGE_01_00_033_02; 13 pages (Box 33, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 865 to 878.
  - C. A. Parsons, 1914–1930; HaleGE_01_00_033_03; 19 pages (Box 33, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 879 to 898.
  - William Barclay Parsons, 1911–1920; HaleGE_01_00_033_04; 15 pages (Box 33, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 899 to 913.
  - Stewart Paton, 1916–1927; HaleGE_01_00_033_05; 26 pages (Box 33, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 914 to 940.
  - W. W. Payne, 1902–1903; HaleGE_01_00_033_06; 7 pages (Box 33, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 941 to 948.
  - Raymond Pearl, 1916–1928; HaleGE_01_00_033_07; 116 pages (Box 33, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 28, frames 949 to 1066.
  - F. G. Pease, 1918–1934; HaleGE_01_00_033_08; 55 pages (Box 33, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 20 to 75.
  - C. D. Perrine, 1904–1934; HaleGE_01_00_033_09; 80 pages (Box 33, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 76 to 156.
  - O. L. Petitdidier, 1904–1906; HaleGE_01_00_033_10; 17 pages (Box 33, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 157 to 174.
  - W. L. Phelps, 1919–1920; HaleGE_01_00_033_11; 4 pages (Box 33, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 175 to 180.
  - Emile Picard, 1918–1919; HaleGE_01_00_033_12; 35 pages (Box 33, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 181 to 217.
  - Miss Picher, 1911; HaleGE_01_00_033_13; 2 pages (Box 33, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 218 to 220.
  - Edward C. Pickering, 1888–1928; HaleGE_01_00_033_14; 85 pages (Box 33, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 221 to 306.
  - Edward C. Pickering memorial, 1921–1926; HaleGE_01_00_033_15; 13 pages (Box 33, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 307 to 320.
  - Roy S. Pike, 1928; HaleGE_01_00_033_16; 30 pages (Box 33, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 321 to 351.
  - R. W. Pike, 1897–1898; HaleGE_01_00_033_17; 5 pages (Box 33, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 352 to 357.
  - Gifford Pinchot, 1903–1915; HaleGE_01_00_033_18; 40 pages (Box 33, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 358 to 398.
  - E. H. Pitkin, 1900–1901; HaleGE_01_00_033_19; 20 pages (Box 33, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 399 to 419.
  - J. S. Plaskett, 1916–1935; HaleGE_01_00_033_20; 25 pages (Box 33, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 420 to 445.
  - H. C. Plummer, 1924–1931; HaleGE_01_00_033_21; 26 pages (Box 33, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 446 to 472.
  - W. E. Plummer, 1903–1904; HaleGE_01_00_033_22; 14 pages (Box 33, Folder 22)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 473 to 487.
  - Poggendorff, 1902–1933; HaleGE_01_00_033_23; 40 pages (Box 33, Folder 23)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 488 to 528.
  - Charles Lane Poor, 1903–1907; HaleGE_01_00_033_24; 16 pages (Box 33, Folder 24)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 529 to 545.
  - Helen Porter, 1900–1903; HaleGE_01_00_033_25; 7 pages (Box 33, Folder 25)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 546 to 553.
  - Russell Porter, 1928–1936; HaleGE_01_00_033_26; 60 pages (Box 33, Folder 26)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 554 to 614.
  - E. Potter, 1917; HaleGE_01_00_033_27; 14 pages (Box 33, Folder 27)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 615 to 629.
  - Henry N. Potter, 1918; HaleGE_01_00_033_28; 2 pages (Box 33, Folder 28)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 630 to 632.
  - Gertrude Pratt, 1902; HaleGE_01_00_033_29; 4 pages (Box 33, Folder 29)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 633 to 637.
  - John S. Prince, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_033_30; 12 pages (Box 33, Folder 30)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 638 to 650.
  - H. S. Pritchett, 1900–1946; HaleGE_01_00_033_31; 414 pages (Box 33, Folder 31, Box 34, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 651 to 1065.
  - Mary Proctor, 1913–1926; HaleGE_01_00_034_02; 14 pages (Box 34, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 1066 to 1080.
  - C. Pulfrich, 1903–1904; HaleGE_01_00_034_03; 6 pages (Box 34, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 1081 to 1087.
  - P. Puiseux, 1911; HaleGE_01_00_034_04; 4 pages (Box 34, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 1088 to 1090.
  - M. I. Pupin, 1914–1916; HaleGE_01_00_034_05; 18 pages (Box 34, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 29, frames 1091 to 1112.
  - Osgood Putnam, 1915–1917; HaleGE_01_00_034_06; 6 pages (Box 34, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 20 to 26.
  - K. B. Quinan, 1920–1923; HaleGE_01_00_034_07; 24 pages (Box 34, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 27 to 51.
  - C. H. Randall, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_034_08; 4 pages (Box 34, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 52 to 56.
  - Miss Ransom and Miss Bridges School, 1912–1915; HaleGE_01_00_034_09; 32 pages (Box 34, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 57 to 89.
  - K. Vaikunta Rao, 1925–1926; HaleGE_01_00_034_10; 39 pages (Box 34, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 90 to 127.
  - Lord Rayleigh, 1907–1932; HaleGE_01_00_034_11; 38 pages (Box 34, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 128 to 166.
  - W. B. Rayton, 1930–1936; HaleGE_01_00_034_12; 28 pages (Box 34, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 167 to 195.
  - Eugenio Regnano, 1909; HaleGE_01_00_034_13; 8 pages (Box 34, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 196 to 204.
  - J. K. Rees, 1898–1901; HaleGE_01_00_034_14; 15 pages (Box 34, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 205 to 219.
  - Ira Remsen, 1903–1914; HaleGE_01_00_034_15; 35 pages (Box 34, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 220 to 255.
  - Stanley Reynolds, 1928–1929; HaleGE_01_00_034_16; 15 pages (Box 34, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 256 to 271.
  - A. Ricco, 1904–1917; HaleGE_01_00_034_17; 259 pages (Box 34, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 272 to 531.
  - Calvin W. Rice, 1915–1933; HaleGE_01_00_034_18; 39 pages (Box 34, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 532 to 571.
  - T. W. Richards, 1916–1932; HaleGE_01_00_034_19; 17 pages (Box 34, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 572 to 589.
  - F. K. Richtmyer, 1921; HaleGE_01_00_034_20; 24 pages (Box 34, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 590 to 614.
  - A. F. Riggs, 1927–1929; HaleGE_01_00_034_21; 21 pages (Box 34, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 615 to 637.
  - G. W. Ritchey, 1898–1930; HaleGE_01_00_035_01; 90 pages (Box 35, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 638 to 727.
  - Henry M. Robinson, 1915–1937; HaleGE_01_00_035_02; 144 pages (Box 35, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 728 to 871.
  - John D. Rockefeller, Jr., 1932; HaleGE_01_00_035_03; 1 pages (Box 35, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 872 to 873.
  - Austin F. Rogers, 1918; HaleGE_01_00_035_04; 11 pages (Box 35, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 874 to 885.
  - C. E. Rood, 1901; HaleGE_01_00_035_05; 6 pages (Box 35, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 886 to 892.
  - Elihu Root, 1912–1935; HaleGE_01_00_035_06; 132 pages (Box 35, Folder 6)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 893 to 1025.
  - E. B. Rosa, 1914–1916; HaleGE_01_00_035_07; 11 pages (Box 35, Folder 7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 1026 to 1036.
  - Wickliffe Rose, 1924–1932; HaleGE_01_00_035_08; 120 pages (Box 35, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 30, frames 1037 to 1157.
  - Julius Rosenwald, 1917–1926; HaleGE_01_00_035_09; 16 pages (Box 35, Folder 9)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 19 to 35.
  - F. E. Ross, 1928–1934; HaleGE_01_00_035_10; 36 pages (Box 35, Folder 10)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 36 to 72.
  - Abbott Lawrence Rotch, 1899–1904; HaleGE_01_00_035_11; 3 pages (Box 35, Folder 11)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 73 to 76.
  - H. Rubens, undated; HaleGE_01_00_035_12; 3 pages (Box 35, Folder 12)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 77 to 80.
  - Kate Ruel, 1914–1915; HaleGE_01_00_035_13; 13 pages (Box 35, Folder 13)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 81 to 93.
  - Karl Runge, 1926; HaleGE_01_00_035_14; 4 pages (Box 35, Folder 14)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 94 to 98.
  - Henry Norris Russell, 1917–1930; HaleGE_01_00_035_15; 106 pages (Box 35, Folder 15)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 99 to 205.
  - Ernest Rutherford, 1907–1924; HaleGE_01_00_035_16; 64 pages (Box 35, Folder 16)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 206 to 270.
  - H. A. Rust, 1900–1902; HaleGE_01_00_035_17; 3 pages (Box 35, Folder 17)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 271 to 274.
  - Harris J. Ryan, 1919; HaleGE_01_00_035_18; 6 pages (Box 35, Folder 18)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 275 to 281.
  - M. A. Sacksteder, 1904; HaleGE_01_00_035_19; 1 pages (Box 35, Folder 19)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 282 to 283.
  - Prof. R. D. Salisbury, 1903–1904; HaleGE_01_00_035_20; 3 pages (Box 35, Folder 20)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 284 to 287.
  - R. A. Sampson, 1912; HaleGE_01_00_035_21; 3 pages (Box 35, Folder 21)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 288 to 291.
  - San Pedro, 1917–1918; HaleGE_01_00_036_01; 284 pages (Box 36, Folder 1)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 292 to 575.
  - George Sarton, Isis, 1916–1935; HaleGE_01_00_036_02; 127 pages (Box 36, Folder 2)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 576 to 704.
  - W. L. Saunders, 1916; HaleGE_01_00_036_03; 6 pages (Box 36, Folder 3)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 705 to 711.
  - Albert Sauveur, 1917; HaleGE_01_00_036_04; 2 pages (Box 36, Folder 4)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 712 to 714.
  - Walter B. Scaife, 1919–1920; HaleGE_01_00_036_05; 14 pages (Box 36, Folder 5)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 715 to 729.
  - James A. B. Scherer, 1907–1935; HaleGE_01_00_036_06; 474 pages (Box 36, Folder 6–7)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 31, frames 730 to 1205.
  - Paul and Margaret Scherer, 1917–1934; HaleGE_01_00_036_08; 100 pages (Box 36, Folder 8)
    This folder is represented in the microfilm edition of the Hale Papers by reel 32, frames 20 to 123.
  - F. Schiaparelli, 1909–1910; HaleGE_01_00_036_09; 19 pages (Box 36, Folder 9)